<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--Free Company-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FCOMPANY">
			<Text>Free Company</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_FCOMPANY">
			<Text>This Unit is much cheaper than the Pikeman, can pillage without using any movement points, and receives full XP from the City when purchased. Steals gold when attacking a City. May move immediately after purchase.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May only be purchased with [ICON_GOLD] Gold after completing the [COLOR_MAGENTA]Authority[ENDCOLOR] Policy Branch.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FCOMPANY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Free Company are the first mercenary units made available by the completion of the Authority policy tree. Even though they can't be directly produced, they constitute a direct improvement in term of combat prowess over the Pikeman, while gaining some additionnal advantages.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Because they can move immediatly and with full experience when bought, you can field a large number of them very quickly if you have the gold. Furthermore, these scoundrels benefit greatly from offensive warfare thanks to their ability to pillage without movement cost and gain gold whenever they inflict damages to cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_FCOMPANY_TEXT">
			<Text>Where opportunity meets warfare and lawlessness, the life of a soldier can turn quickly to brigandry.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Free Companies, also known as Great Companies or Companies of Adventurers, were bands of mercenary soldiers that operated throughout Europe from the 12th to the early 15th century. Often employed by nobles, they were known for their disregard for the laws of arms and usefulness as raiders. The Free Companies are most famous for their role during the unending conflicts of the 14th century, employed by the English to terrorize the French countryside during the Hundred Years' War.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]While the Companies had work during wartime, they could become a scourge in times of peace; they often took to pillaging the lands of their former employers as soon as they stopped being paid to pillage someone else's. After the Peace of Bretigny in 1360, the Free Companies were released from their service and became uncontrollable. They went from fief to fief, attacking farms and castles alike, operating throughout western Europe and even managing to win against armies fielded against them. The peace and the Plague helped these bands grow in size and audacity, gaining wealth and infamy as they went abroad. Notable companies of this time included the White Company in Italy, the Catalan Company in Greece, and the Tard-Venus in France. Many of these adventurers gained considerable political power from their exploits, such as the Englishman John Hawkwood, who became a wealthy condottiere hired by several Italian states and the Pope.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The rebuilding of Western European states and the formation of professional armies and effective militias during the 15th century brought an end to the use of mercenaries' power. However, the death and destruction wrought by the Free Companies left a deep scar on the European memory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Doppelsöldner promotion-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_DOPPELSOLDNER">
			<Text>Doppelsöldner</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_DOPPELSOLDNER_HELP">
			<Text>+30%[ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength when attacking Units at full health.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>		