<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 4/26/2014 11:18:07 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WTC">
			<Text>World Trade Center</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WTC_HELP">
			<Text>Requires [COLOR_MAGENTA]Prosperity[ENDCOLOR]. Grants 2 additional Delegates in the World Congress. Gain 1 additional Trade Route, and a free Caravan appears in the city. +1 [ICON_RES_PAPER] Paper and a Civil Servant Specialist.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WTC_STRATEGY">
			<Text>This National Wonder cannot be built unless the city has a Wire Service. Build this national wonder to receive additional Delegates in the World Congress, and an additional Trade Route. You will also receive a Paper Resource to build diplomatic units and a Civil Servant to further your diplomatic agenda.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WTC_PEDIA">
			<Text>The World Trade Center was a complex of buildings in New York City, that are currently being replaced with new structures after the original was destroyed. The original World Trade Center featured landmark twin towers, which opened on April 4, 1973, and were destroyed in the September 11th terrorist attacks of 2001, along with 7 World Trade Center. The other buildings in the complex were severely damaged by the collapse of the twin towers, and their ruins were eventually demolished. The original World Trade Center was thought of as a North American cultural icon, and at the time of their completion, the "Twin Towers", the original 1 World Trade Center (the North Tower), at 417 metres (1,368 ft), and 2 World Trade Center (the South Tower), were the tallest buildings in the world. The other buildings in the complex included the Marriott World Trade Center (3 WTC), 4 WTC, 5 WTC, 6 WTC, and 7 WTC. All of these buildings were built between 1975 and 1985, with a construction cost of $400 million. The complex was located in New York City's Financial District and contained 13.4 million square feet (1.24 million m2) of office space.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On the morning of September 11, 2001, Al-Qaeda-affiliated hijackers flew two Boeing 767 jets into the complex, one into each tower, in a coordinated act of terrorism. After burning for 56 minutes, the South Tower collapsed, followed a half-hour later by the North Tower. The attacks on the World Trade Center killed 2,753 people. Falling debris from the towers, combined with fires that the debris initiated in several surrounding buildings, led to the partial or complete collapse of all the other buildings in the complex and caused catastrophic damage to ten other large structures in the surrounding area (including the World Financial Center). The process of cleaning up and recovery at the World Trade Center site took eight months.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Over the following years, plans were created for the reconstruction of the World Trade Center. The Lower Manhattan Development Corporation (LMDC), established in November 2001 to oversee the rebuilding process, organized competitions to select a site plan and memorial design. The first new building at the site was the 7 World Trade Center, which opened in May 2006. The memorial section of the National September 11 Memorial and Museum opened on September 11, 2011 and the museum is expected to open in spring 2014. Construction of the One World Trade Center, also named "Freedom Tower", is nearing completion and it is expected to open in 2014; the 4 World Trade Center opened on November 13, 2013; the 3 World Trade Center is under construction and expected to open in 2016; as of November 2013, according to an agreement made with Silverstein Properties Inc., the 2 World Trade Center will not be built to its full height until sufficient leasing is established to make the building financially viable; and 5 World Trade Center will be developed by the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, but, as of February 2014, a schedule was not confirmed.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>